thank you for attending today's pivotal
感谢您参加今天的重要活动
webcast
网络直播
a bit about the on24 interface before we
关于on24接口的一些知识
begin at the bottom of your audience
从观众的底部开始
console or application components
控制台或应用程序组件
including QA resources health and media
包括质量检查资源，健康和媒体
your audio is being screened through
您的音频正在通过筛选
your computer and speakers you can
您的电脑和扬声器，您可以
expand the center slide area by clicking
通过单击扩展中心幻灯片区域
on the maximize icon on the top right or
在右上方的最大化图标上，或
bottom right corners for technical
技术右下角
difficulty please click on the help icon
困难，请点击帮助图标
at the bottom of the console or use the
在控制台底部或使用
Q&amp;A component on the upper right hand
右上角的问答组件
side of your screen we encourage you to
屏幕的一侧，我们鼓励您
ask questions throughout the webcast to
在整个网络广播中向
see responses for yours and other
查看您和其他人的回应
participant questions use the refresh
参与者问题使用刷新
link throughout the event the resource
在整个活动中链接资源
list on the upper left-hand side of your
在您的左上角列出
console contains supporting resources
控制台包含支持资源
with clickable links for you to view
带有可点击链接供您查看
including a link for the video replay
包括视频重播的链接
enjoy today's presentation good morning
早上好享受今天的演讲
to the west coast and good afternoon
到西海岸，下午好
from the East Coast
从东海岸
my name is Dan Ken and I work for a
我的名字叫Dan Ken，我为
company called IAC applications based in
公司称为IAC应用程序基于
New York City I am a member of the
纽约市，我是
rat-pack core team and today we'll be
鼠包核心团队，今天我们将成为
talking about spring boot and rat-pack
谈论 spring boot 和鼠尾包
web framework and why you should be
网络框架以及为什么要这么做
using both of them
同时使用它们
so let's talk a little bit about spring
所以让我们谈谈 Spring
boot we you know spring as a the
引导，我们知道 Spring 是
framework in as an ecosystem has been
作为生态系统的框架
around for more than 10 years right and
大约十多年了
spring MVC specifically spring web MVC
spring MVC特别是spring web MVC
specifically has also been around for
特别是也有
more than 10 years so when you consider
超过10年，所以当您考虑
a library that has that kind of
具有这种类型的图书馆
longevity but also just sheer market
长寿，但也只是纯粹的市场
dominance we're talking about a really
优势，我们正在谈论一个真正的
solid library that you can really depend
您可以真正依赖的可靠库
on and in fact many people do every
实际上，很多人都在做
single day if we take a look in spring
如果我们在 Spring 看一天
in maven central we look for the
在Maven Central，我们寻找
original spring of webbing see the
织带的原始Spring
earliest one I could find was when 102
我最早可以找到的时候是102
that was released in 2005 it's 2006 16
在2005年发行的2006年16
now and the the framework has actually
现在，该框架实际上已经
grown quite nicely with the changing
随着变化的不断发展
times
次
all all while you know maintaining
当你知道维护的时候
backwards-compatibility to the best to
向后兼容
the best of their ability until you know
尽力而为，直到您知道
it's time to shut things down in the AP
是时候关闭AP中的内容了
life in the AP island but um spring boot
生活在AP岛上，但 spring boot
really takes all that experience and
真的需要所有这些经验，
turns it into a a really pleasant
变成一个非常愉快的
development experience some of the
开发经验的一些
changes that are emphasized in spring
Spring 强调的变化
fruit is that you know you should create
果是你知道你应该创造
a self-contained artifact whether that's
一个独立的人工制品是否
a jar or an executable war file or even
一个jar或可执行的war文件，甚至
a war file that deploys to a servlet
部署到servlet的war文件
container whatever your needs are
容器，无论您需要什么
whatever your operational needs are
无论您的运营需求是什么
Spring boot can obviously tell that
Spring Boot显然可以告诉我们
another thing about spring boot is that
关于 spring boot 的另一件事是
we really don't want to use XML at all
我们真的根本不想使用XML
XML not only like looks very verbose and
XML不仅看起来很冗长而且
it's hard to type out by memory but um
很难通过内存输入，但是
it's not it's not really type safe so if
不是，不是真正的类型安全，所以如果
you're trying to instantiate your your
您正在尝试实例化您的
application context with all your beams
您的所有应用程序上下文
and all you have our XML nodes looking
和所有您拥有我们的XML节点
at each other I mean IDs these days
我彼此的意思是这些天的ID
really help you in terms of matching
确实对您有帮助
beans and making sure that they fit but
bean 并确保它们适合但
you know let's just say you're using the
您知道我们只是说您正在使用
standard text editor like that's not
像这样的标准文本编辑器
going to help you at all so in spring
会在春季完全帮助您
frameworks context library there are a
框架上下文库中有一个
series of annotations that help you
一系列有助于您的注释
provide a Java mechanism for defining
提供用于定义的Java机制
spring beans and it's called a
Spring bean ，它被称为
configuration there is an annotation at
配置中有一个注释
configuration which is able to declare
能够声明的配置
you know a simple class with with
你知道一个简单的课程
additional annotations like at being and
其他注释，例如at和
things like that that allow you to
这样的事情可以让你
define your beans in Java code such huge
用如此巨大的Java代码定义bean
advantages you know you got compile
你知道的优势，你可以编译
verification compile time verification
验证编译时间验证
that you're being there all ok and yeah
你在那里都很好，是的
it said that's the programmatic way of
它说这是程序化的方式
defining a bean structure
定义一个bean结构
Springwood also has a big emphasis on
斯普林伍德也非常重视
integrating with some of the best
与一些最好的集成
libraries that are out there in the jvm
jvm中存在的库
ecosystem so in particular spring cloud
生态系统，尤其是 Spring Cloud
comes to mind
浮现在脑海
spring cloud project has a whole bunch
Spring Cloud 项目有很多
of libraries in it things that enable
库中的东西使
you to have auto service discovery let's
您可以进行自动服务发现
say if you're in distributor
说出您是否在经销商中
architecture so that you know you can
建筑，以便您知道您可以
you can you can add just like a single
您可以像添加一个一样
annotation and your service can you know
注解和您的服务您知道吗
automatically know where to look up for
自动知道在哪里寻找
where does this service live where is
该服务在哪里生活
that service live or I'm the service and
该服务是现场服务还是我是服务，
I'm and I'm registering as a part of
我正在注册成为
this group here so I mean the value of
这个小组在这里，我的意思是
using a project like spring boot has all
使用像spring boot这样的项目
the value of using any kind of Spring
使用任何一种Spring的价值
Framework as I mentioned earlier it's an
如前所述，框架是
industry standard I don't think you'll
行业标准，我认为您不会
find any JVM based shop out there that
在那找到任何基于JVM的商店
has never used spring before the using a
在使用a之前从未使用过spring
project like spring booth lets you focus
春季展台之类的项目让您专注
on writing business logic like right out
正确编写业务逻辑
the gate and prove you know people
门，证明你认识人
coming onto projects or you know you
参加项目或者你知道你
know switching projects are coming
知道交换项目即将到来
through companies or things like that
通过公司或类似的东西
because everybody knows to bring and
因为每个人都知道带来
because you're really focused on many
因为你真的专注于很多
components everybody from all skill
每个人的全部技能
groups you know from beginners to
从初学者到
interns to senior developers so on and
实习到高级开发人员等等
so forth they have an immediate impact
等等，它们立即产生影响
and they just start writing code and I
他们才开始编写代码，而我
think that's that's really invaluable so
认为那是非常宝贵的，所以
getting started with spring boot
spring boot 入门
I mean first I recommend you know
我的意思是首先我建议你知道
visiting the spring blue page on the
前往网页上的春季蓝页
official spring site they have a whole
春季官方网站，他们有一个整体
bunch of grey guides here the
一堆灰色指南
documentation is amazing the Java Doc's
文档很棒Java Doc的
are amazing is very well documented and
令人惊讶的是有据可查
plenty of examples to go around one of
很多例子可以解决以下问题之一
my favorite ways to get started with a
我最喜欢的入门方式
spring boot application however is
Spring Boot应用程序是
through the spring initializer so if you
通过Spring 初始化器，所以如果你
go to start that spring that IO can come
去那年 Spring 开始IO可以来
in
在
spring doesn't really care right like
Spring 真的不在乎
about what kind of built system you use
关于您使用哪种内置系统
they support the to industry standards
他们支持行业标准
here which are maven and Gradle and you
这是Maven和Gradle，而您
can specify your version of spring boot
可以指定您的Spring Boot版本
that you'd like to use and you know this
您想使用的并且您知道这一点
little search box here allows you to add
小搜索框可让您添加
libraries that are associated with
与之相关的库
starter packages and spring boots
入门包和 spring boot
starter packages are a collaboration
入门包是一个协作
between spring team and all the various
在 The Spring Team 和所有各种球队之间
frameworks that are out there that
在那里的框架
provides basically the one annotation
基本上提供一个注释
based import that you need to provide on
您需要提供的基于基础的导入
your main spring boot class and you get
你的主要 spring boot 类，你得到
all this functionality for free we
所有这些功能都是免费的，我们
switch to the full version you can
切换到完整版本即可
actually see there's a whole bunch of
其实看到有一堆
stuff down there like this is this is
像这样的东西是这个
the value of spring boot right this is
spring boot 的值对，这是
the the spring ecosystem really like you
Spring 的生态系统真的很喜欢你
have all of these available for you any
有所有这些可供您使用
kind of concern that you have again like
你再次喜欢的那种关注
around we're doing cloud stuff you know
周围我们正在做云的东西，你知道
you want to make sure that your
您要确保您的
discovery is just taken care of your
发现只是照顾您的
outings taken care of that you have like
郊游照顾你喜欢
a robust - robust architecture set up
强大的架构
like if you're going with micro service
就像您要使用微服务一样
architecture things like logging it's
体系结构之类的日志记录
just this is really invaluable you can
只是这真的很宝贵
come in here click off whatever you want
进来这里，按一下你想要的
there's a generate project and it'll
有一个生成项目，它将
it'll download a zip file with
它会下载一个zip文件
everything that you need to get started
入门所需的一切
really invaluable resource so let's say
真正宝贵的资源，所以说
we do want to get started with a screen
我们确实想从屏幕开始
boot I've gone ahead and created a basic
启动我已经开始并创建了一个基本的
project here and
项目在这里和
this project has consisted three modules
这个项目包括三个模块
which really sit side by side and I am
真正并肩而坐的我
going with a griddle based configuration
使用基于网格的配置
the first thing that I want to introduce
我想介绍的第一件事
to you is just on something that
对你来说只是在
represents a stereotypical artifact that
代表一个定型工件
you would find your company's the Nexus
您会发现您公司的Nexus
repository as an example so the
储存库为例
build.gradle file for this is is pretty
这个的build.gradle文件很漂亮
simple we just depend upon spring core
简单，我们只依赖于Spring Core
for dependency injection and we depend
依赖注入，我们依赖
upon the spring context here so you know
在这里的 Spring ，所以你知道
you can imagine that you would go
你可以想象你会去
through your application and you have
通过您的应用程序，您已经
been-- definitions and perhaps you know
曾经的定义，也许你知道
your you have some JPA stuff set up or
您已经设置了一些JPA内容，或者
whatever so for those not familiar with
对于不熟悉的人如何
Java configuration which has been around
Java配置已经存在
for a while now but hasn't been
好一阵子了，但是还没有
popularized I would argue until perhaps
普及，我会争论直到
spring food is uh this this is now your
春季食品是这个，这就是你的
replacement for the XML for your you
为您替换XML
know application context XML so you can
了解应用程序上下文XML，因此您可以
think of this whole class as that
把整个班级都认为
application context XML document
应用程序上下文XML文档
documentation we have three beings
文档，我们有三个存在
defined here by default I do believe
我相信默认情况下在这里定义
these are scoped as Singleton's and the
这些的范围为Singleton和
beans are defined by their types as you
Bean由您的类型定义
can see and then their implementation so
可以看到然后执行
you know our string bean is just some
你知道我们的四季 bean 只是一些
kind of important message web you know
您知道的一种重要消息网
an important business service which is
一个重要的商业服务是
just you know a simple interface just
只是您知道一个简单的界面而已
makes money and we also have a message
赚钱，我们也有一个消息
service which is just send some kind of
只是发送某种服务
messaging so you know like there's
消息传递，所以您知道就像
really not much to it and as I was
真的没有什么和我一样
emphasizing earlier you know if you have
早点强调你知道你是否有
some kind of like dependency injection
某种类似的依赖注入
going on this is how it would be
这是怎么回事
accomplished so this secret message
完成了，所以这个秘密信息
would actually be injected by injected
实际上会被注入
with this secret message being that's
这个秘密消息就是
defined earlier on as with all things
早先定义为所有事物
like being order doesn't kind of
就像被命令不是那种
actually doesn't matter in terms of
其实并没有关系
declaration because spring will
声明，因为 Spring 会
great proxies and you do whatever needs
出色的代理，您可以做任何需要的事情
to do so yeah are these are just our
这样做是的，这些只是我们的
basic limitations of our interfaces and
我们界面的基本局限性
is our collection of three beams this is
是我们的三个光束的集合，这是
this is something this is this module is
这是这个模块的东西
just supposed to represent you know that
只是代表您知道
artifact that you would carry around
你会随身携带的神器
with you so I just want to show you her
和你在一起，所以我只想告诉你她
spring boot getting started with spring
Spring Boot春季入门
boot our Gradle build for spring boot
启动我们的Gradle构建以进行 spring boot
I've taken a couple of things out or not
我已经拿了几件事
a couple of things in so in Gradle since
自从Gradle以来有几件事
our spring configuration projects it's
我们的春季配置项目是
side-by-side with with the spring brute
与 Spring 的野蛮人并排
demo and the rat-pack demo we have a
演示和rat-pack演示，我们有一个
dependency upon the spring configuration
对Spring 配置的依赖
so so this will compile that artifact
所以这将编译该工件
and bring it into the project and put on
并把它带到项目中并穿上
this class I should mention here that
这个课我应该在这里提到
this you couldn't really do this with uh
这你真的不能用呃做
with maven with maven you would have to
与Maven与Maven，你将不得不
you know publish the thing to your local
你知道把东西发布到你当地的
maven and uh and then pull it in and
Maven和恩，然后将其拉入并
this kind of um
这种嗯
maven standard format where you have
您拥有的Maven标准格式
your group artifact and your version
您的小组工件和您的版本
coordinates so a couple of things I want
协调了我想要的几件事
to point out here because we're using
在这里指出，因为我们正在使用
Gradle and we did download this from the
Gradle，我们确实是从
spring initializer we actually have the
Spring 初始化我们实际上有
spring initializer applies a Gradle
Spring 初始化器应用Gradle
plugin for spring boot and this is
spring boot 插件，这是
provided by the screen for booth spring
屏幕提供的展位Spring
routine
常规
so this plugin provides a couple of
所以这个插件提供了几个
really cool things one of which is if
真的很酷的事情之一是
you notice this compile time dependency
您会注意到此编译时间依赖性
here on spring good starter web
在春季良好的入门网站上
you'll notice that there's no version at
您会注意到这里没有版本
the end of this and typically when you
结束，通常是当你
use a project like spring boot you're
使用像Spring Boot这样的项目
bringing in more than just you know one
带来的不仅仅是你认识的一个
or two libraries you're you're probably
或您所拥有的两个图书馆
bringing in spring security you're
带来Spring Security 保障
bringing in web WC you're bringing in
引入您正在引入的Web WC
data perhaps hibernate whatever else is
数据可能会休眠
available but if you refer back to that
可用，但如果您再参考一下
page there are a ton of integrations for
页面上有大量的集成
spring boot when you apply the spring
使用Spring 时的 spring boot
boot plugin it'll actually make sure
启动插件，它实际上将确保
that all of these versions are in
所有这些版本都在
lockstep with each other so that you
彼此同步，以便您
maintain a binary compatibility and
保持二进制兼容性并
these versions will be locked into this
这些版本将被锁定到此
spring blue version that's exposed up
暴露的 Spring 蓝色版本
here for those not familiar with groovy
对于那些不熟悉groovy的人
because because Gradle is essentially a
因为Gradle本质上是
groovy DSL the dependencies for this
groovy DSL的依赖关系
build script gear has this kind of funky
构建脚本齿轮具有这种时髦
syntax but if your user a spring and use
语法，但如果您的用户是Spring 和使用
a spring expression language that should
应该使用的 Spring Expression Language
look kind of familiar to you what we
看起来对您来说很熟悉
have going on here is just a groovy
发生在这里只是一个时髦
string interpolation dub this is nice
字符串插值配音，这很好
because you know instead of repeating
因为你知道而不是重复
this whole bunch of times which we're
这整个时期，我们
already avoiding by using the spring
已经避免使用Spring
blue plug-in you can kind of define this
蓝色插件，您可以对此进行定义
in this some externalized key value
在这个外在的关键价值
pairs that uh that's a great song
配对，那是一首很棒的歌
construct so a really nice way to keep
构造一个非常好的保持方式
all your versions locked down in one
您所有的版本都锁定在一个
place but other than that to get a
的地方，但除此之外获得一个
minimal spring good application this is
最小的Spring 良好的应用程序，这是
really the only this is really the only
真的唯一的，这是真的唯一的
dependency you need and even this
你需要的依赖，甚至这个
dependency is overkill because it brings
依赖过大，因为它带来
in spring engine see spring boot
在Spring 引擎中查看Spring 启动
applications don't have to be web
应用程序不必是网络
applications they can be command line
可以作为命令行的应用程序
applications again like you know come
再次像您知道的应用程序来
back to our Acme configuration like this
回到我们的Acme配置
is our spring context you know if you
是我们的 Spring 背景，您知道是否
have all your bean graph setup and you
设置好所有 bean 图，然后
want to create a command line
要创建命令行
application that runs a cron job but you
运行cron作业的应用程序，但是您
need your you know your object route to
需要您知道您的目标路线
be present this is a great way to do it
在场，这是做到这一点的好方法
you just bring in you can bring back
你带进去就可以带回来
because bigger made a configuration into
因为更大的配置
the spring good command line class and
Spring 的好命令行课程和
just hook it up and go
挂上去
so let's take a look at what spring drew
所以让我们看一下 Spring 所吸引的
in hello world looks like I just want to
在你好世界看起来我只是想
take a moment and reflect on the brevity
花一点时间思考一下简洁
of this class we take a look at nothing
本课我们什么也不看
line numbers right including new lines
行号正确，包括新行
and all we have 22 lines and when you
我们共有22行，当您
think about it like if you think way
想一想就好了
back to like spring MBC to five let's
回到像 Spring MBC到五个
say or even like spring 3o like pre 31
说或什至像春季3o一样pre 31
MVC you know like the setting up a
您知道的MVC喜欢设置
spring application was actually like
春季申请实际上就像
better than the alternatives out there
比那里的替代品更好
right like setting up like a Jada Lee
就像贾达·李一样
application server as an example but um
以应用服务器为例，但是
you still have to concern yourself with
你仍然要关心自己
a whole bunch of XML in the form of your
一堆XML以您的形式
WebEx mo signing you know registering
您知道要注册的WebEx Mo签名
that spring dispatcher servlet right to
该Spring 调度程序servlet有权
abstract away all of your application
提取所有应用程序
code from the certain container
来自特定容器的代码
you know perhaps if you had application
你知道也许你有申请
context XML and bringing all that in and
上下文XML，并将所有内容带入
supreme food really takes you know those
至高无上的食物真的会让你知道那些
years of experience in terms of creating
多年的创作经验
these applications and distilled it down
这些应用程序，并蒸馏下来
to this 22 line file or here you have a
到这个22行文件，或者在这里
minimally viable application that you
您最不可行的应用程序
know binds to a get request against the
知道绑定到针对
route path and returns a point text
路由路径并返回点文本
response and this is all tix I want to
响应，这就是我想要的所有提示
point out that um that we have you know
指出我们知道的那个
two annotations here the one that may be
这里有两个注释，可能是
new to you is the spring food
对您来说新鲜的是春季食品
application this one enables
这个启用的应用
auto-configuration
自动配置
you know component scanning bringing in
你知道组件扫描带来的
spring MVC you know all that good stuff
春季MVC，您知道所有这些好东西
that enables you to write this really
可以让您真正写出
concise class the controller annotation
简洁的类控制器注释
you should be familiar with by now if
您现在应该已经熟悉
you've been using spring MVC for awhile
您已经使用Spring MVC已有一段时间了
and of course some you know are to
当然你知道一些
request based annotations will inform
基于请求的注释将通知
spring embassy about this endpoint
Spring 大使馆关于这个终点
so yeah let's let's just take a quick
是的，让我们快速
look at what sending a request against
看看发送请求的对象
this kind of application looks like okay
这种应用看起来还不错
I have a previous institution running
我以前有一个机构在运作
let's run that again all right so we're
让我们再次运行它，所以我们
up and running pretty quick right quick
快速启动并运行
- right it's quick to get up and if we
-是的，起床很快，如果我们
issue a request against default port
针对默认端口发出请求
that everyone knows and loves port 8080
大家都知道并喜欢8080端口
we do see indeed that we get back our
我们确实确实看到我们重新获得了我们的
hello world and if we just turn on
你好，世界，如果我们只是打开
verbosity to see where requests look
详细了解请求的位置
like we can see that you know Apache
就像我们看到您了解Apache
coyote 1 1 is the server that's being
土狼1 1是服务器
set this response header and also that
设置这个响应头，还有
we're returning as plaintext encoded as
我们以编码为
utf-8 so this is um I mean this is this
utf-8，所以这是嗯，我的意思是这个
is quite compelling right to get off the
下车的权利非常引人注目
ground running takes almost no time
地面运行几乎不需要时间
especially if you just go to the spring
特别是如果你去 Spring
initializer download the artifact and
初始化程序下载工件并
just run the application like you're
就像你一样运行应用程序
already off the ground at the click of a
只需单击一下就可以了
button and I think that's really
按钮，我认为那是真的
compelling if you're not using spring
如果您不使用spring，那么令人信服
butperhaps yet nice this is this should
但也许还不错，这应该是
at least get you a little bit curious
至少让你有点好奇
about what the possibilities can be like
关于可能性是什么样的
using a supreme boot
使用最高引导
so yep I just I just want to point out
是的，我只是想指出
again right there's no application
再次正确，没有申请
context XML there's no web.xml you don't
上下文XML，没有没有的web.xml
have to like guess or you know Google
必须喜欢猜测，或者您知道Google
what goes where you just put annotations
你刚刚放注释的地方
on and you're good to go
继续，你很好走
there's also no compact configuration to
也没有紧凑的配置
play around with but again if you needed
一起玩，但如果需要的话再玩一次
to get access to any of that kind of
可以访问任何一种
stuff
东西
bring this documentation is amazing you
带上这份文件真是太神奇了
should be able to just go in there and
应该能够就在那里
figure out what you need to do so that's
弄清楚你需要做什么，那就是
a little background on spring boot let's
spring boot 的一些背景让我们
talk about Rat Pack so Rat Pack Rat Pack
谈论Rat Pack，所以Rat Pack Rat Pack
is hosted at a Rat Pack guy oh this is a
主持人是Rat Pack的家伙，哦，这是
good hub repository from the
好的枢纽仓库
organization for the repository here but
此处存储库的组织，但
uh let's talk about Rat Pack so Rat Pack
恩，我们来谈谈Rat Pack，所以Rat Pack
is a set of Java libraries you can you
是一组Java库，您可以
can think of them as jars they're just a
可以将它们视为罐子，它们只是一个
charts
图表
what are these jars do they let you
这些罐子让你做什么
serve HTTP requests and a whole bunch of
服务HTTP请求和一堆
other good stuff along with it so it's
其他好的东西，所以它是
the the entire project is at a minimum
整个项目最少
of Java 8 so you'll need to be on Java
Java 8版本，因此您需要使用Java
eighties Rat Pack another very important
八十年代鼠包另一个非常重要
thing to point out is that Rat Pack has
指出的是Rat Pack有
no knowledge of the servlet API it's not
不了解servlet API，不是
a part of our runtime class path we
我们的运行时类路径的一部分
don't compile against it we don't
不反对它，我们不反对
implement any of it but we do provide
实施其中任何一项，但我们确实提供
analogs for all servlet API constructs
所有Servlet API构造的类似物
like you know HTTP request objects
就像您知道HTTP请求对象一样
response object sessions cookies headers
响应对象会话cookie标头
all that good stuff we don't have you
所有那些我们没有的好东西
know because it's not a servlet
知道，因为它不是servlet
implementation we don't deploy to a
我们不会部署到
servlet container there's no more file
servlet容器中没有更多文件
you just build a jar file and you're
你只要建立一个jar文件，
good to go
好去
math pack is lightly opinionated I say
我说数学包有些自以为是
lightly because you know we do emphasize
轻率地因为你知道我们确实强调
being asynchronous lazy you know using
异步懒惰，您知道使用
like functional approach to writing this
像写这篇文章的功能方法
code making it immutable composable
使之成为不变的代码
and a little asterisk scared that it's
还有一个星号害怕它是
all so reactive as you can see by this
一切都如此反应
ribbon in the upper right hand corner
右上角的功能区
being reactive just means them that
反应性就意味着他们
implements the reactive streams
实现反应流
that's compatibility kit the API really
那就是API的兼容套件
and we passed the test seventy TDK so if
我们通过了70 TDK测试，所以如果
you're familiar with other reactive
您熟悉其他反应式
streaming projects like perhaps rx Java
像rx Java这样的流项目
you can actually use rx Java and rap
您实际上可以使用rx Java和rap
back together yeah there are other
回到一起是的，还有其他
libraries that are out there that
那里的图书馆
implements the reactive streams API yeah
实现反应式流API是的
it's quite easy to implement to
实施起来很容易
integrate it with fatback attack is also
与胖背攻击整合
because it's not you know it's really
因为不是你知道这是真的
base it has to take care of its own
它必须自己照顾
request handling and that's done through
请求处理，并通过
a library called Metis you don't know
一个你不知道的叫做Metis的图书馆
about nutty
关于坚果
it is battle-proven and it is a net-net
它是经过战斗验证的，并且是一个网
is really good about minimum minima
关于最小最小值真的很好
minimizing resources so we're talking
减少资源，所以我们在谈论
about like CPU and memory and yielding
大约像CPU和内存并产生收益
the capacity for doing large volumes
大容量的能力
processing large volumes of HTTP
处理大量HTTP
requests or really any kind of request
请求或实际上任何形式的请求
nati is just the networking framework
nati只是网络框架
and then they do have you know support
然后他们确实有您知道的支持
for HTTP and HTTPS stuff but uh it's not
用于HTTP和HTTPS的东西，但是不是
just limited to http
仅限于http
so just emphasize again Rat Pack just a
所以再次强调Rat Pack只是一个
you know compile time class time
你知道编译时间上课时间
dependency there's no SDK to download
没有SDK下载
there's no code gen that happens Rat
没有代码发生
Pack is definitely not MVC there are no
包绝对不是MVC，没有
controllers here and we certainly don't
控制器在这里，我们当然不会
have views although we do have we do
有意见虽然我们有我们有
support templating and there's no table
支持模板，没有桌子
based routing this is more of a chain of
基于路由，这更多的是
responsibility kind of approach and I'll
责任的方式，我会
get into that a bit another thing about
进入另一件事
Rat Pack is that it's currently at
Rat Pack是它目前在
version 1 200 so we are API stable for
版本1200，因此我们对API稳定
the 100 branch for the 1 dot X line the
1点X线的100分支
Rat Pack
鼠包
it's we've been API stable for about a
我们已经稳定API大约
year now and we do have a small but
一年以来，我们确实有一个小但
growing dedicated community around Rat
围绕Rat成长的敬业社区
Pack and and if you join us in our slack
打包，如果您加入我们的行列
Channel you know people talk about how
您知道的频道人们谈论如何
they're using rap back or what kind of
他们正在使用说唱回声或
questions that they have about using rap
关于说唱的疑问
back so why would you want to use
回来，所以你为什么要使用
something like rap back
像说唱回来
well rap back is what we would consider
好说唱回来，我们会考虑
to be WYSIWYG what you see is what you
成为所见即所得你所看到的就是你
get that is there's no quote-unquote
得到那是没有报价-取消报价
magic meaning you know there's no
魔术，意味着你知道没有
classpath scanning
类路径扫描
no reflection it doesn't it does what
没有反思，不是，它做什么
you tell it to do which for some people
你告诉它为某些人做
they like that for others they they want
他们喜欢他们想要的其他人
things to work out in the box they just
在盒子里解决的事情
want everything to be hooked up and
希望一切都挂钩
connected but that's that's the core
连接，但这就是核心
tenets of rat pack that doesn't mean
鼠包的宗旨并不意味着
that you can't write code around rat
你不能围绕老鼠写代码
pack that does have this quote-unquote
确实有这个quote-unquote的包
magic and indeed some people are
魔术，确实有些人是
actually doing this rat pack is designed
实际做这个老鼠包是设计的
for developer friendliness and
为了开发人员友好和
productivity meaning since there's such
生产力的意义，因为有这样的
there's not much that the rat pack
那只老鼠包没什么
server is actually doing startup and
服务器实际上正在启动，
teardown times the rat pack servers are
拆解时间的大鼠包服务器是
under a second no matter what watch
一秒钟内不管什么手表
shouldn't say no matter what but really
不管怎么说，不应该说
this this leads to productivity because
这导致生产力提高，因为
we enable for development mode hot
我们启用开发模式hot
reloading and it's interesting actually
重新加载，实际上很有趣
because as a spring boot 1/3 rat pack
因为作为 spring boot 1/3鼠装
and spring boot actually have the same
和 spring boot 实际上有相同的
mechanism for doing on pot reloads
锅重装的机制
spring boot as long as you add the dev
spring boot ，只要您添加开发人员
tools that are provided by the spring
Spring 提供的工具
blue team as it detects changes it will
蓝队，因为它检测到变化，它将
you know reload the entire application
你知道重新加载整个应用程序
server simply happens in rat pack if you
服务器只是发生在大鼠包中，如果您
happen to use Gradle we have first-class
碰巧使用Gradle我们有一流的
Gradle support so if you're running rat
摇篮支持，因此，如果您正在运行老鼠
pack through Gradle or you're running it
通过Gradle打包或您正在运行它
through a groovy script as soon as it
尽快通过常规脚本
notices changes it'll restart the server
通知更改它将重新启动服务器
and the blink of an eye
和眨眼
this makes rat pack great for rapid
这使得老鼠包非常适合快速
prototyping and and not just prototyping
原型设计，而不仅仅是原型设计
but actually evolving to a larger
但实际上发展到更大
codebase because we have a lot of
代码库，因为我们有很多
mechanisms around encapsulating pieces
封装件的机制
of data or pieces of behavior rather
数据或行为的一部分
that described how Rat Pack should be
描述了大鼠背包应该如何
handling incoming traffic and it allows
处理传入流量，它允许
you to kind of separate and reuse bits
您要分开并重复使用
of these code in a very nice way another
这些代码以一种非常不错的方式
value about using Rat Pack is because it
使用Rat Pack的价值是因为它
doesn't require as many resources you
不需要您太多的资源
can really reduce that that monthly
真的可以每月减少
footprint on your cloud bill whether
云账单上的足迹是否
you're using AWS or Google cloud
您正在使用AWS或Google云
computer as your whatever you won't have
电脑就是你所没有的
to have as powerful nodes running out
具有强大的节点用尽
there so all the code samples in this
那里的所有代码示例
will be in Java but for this first
将使用Java，但首先
example of hello world in groovy I'm
groovy中的“ hello world”示例
actually for Rat Pack I'm actually going
实际上是为Rat Pack我实际上要去
to write this groovy so the reason the
写这个俗套的原因
reason of course is to show how
原因当然是要展示
compelling it is to use something like
令人信服的是使用类似
this so here is what a rat pack groovy
这就是老鼠包的时髦
application looks like Anna scripts this
应用程序看起来像安娜脚本
grab
抓
annotation is baked into like guru
批注像专家一样烘焙
scripts it's basically a way to grab
脚本，这基本上是一种获取方式
dependencies you know you can use your
你知道你可以使用你的依赖
familiar they have an artifact to your
熟悉，他们对您有人工制品
group group is iota rat-pack
组组是iota rat-pack
the artifact name is that groovy and the
工件名称是groovy和
virgin ears one two which is the latest
处女的耳朵一两个这是最新的
stable version out there we do is we
我们要做的是稳定版本
import this static rat-pack method and
导入此静态rat-pack方法，然后
what the static rat-pack method does is
静态rat-pack方法的作用是
it allows us to start building our
它使我们可以开始构建我们的
server or really describing how the
服务器或真正描述
application should be handling incoming
应用程序应处理传入
requests we define handlers we're
要求我们定义处理程序
talking into a little bit and what we do
谈一点，我们做什么
is we end up finding a handler to the
是我们最终找到了一个处理程序
get of a root request root path request
获取根请求根路径请求
that comes in and what do we do with
进来，我们该怎么办
this we're just going to render hello
这个我们只是要打个招呼
Ruby and that's it this is this is an
Ruby，就是这样，这是一个
entire rat pack application the real
整个大鼠包的实际应用
deal and
处理和
it's just to run this application you
只是为了运行这个应用程序
simply run groovy and then the name of
只需运行groovy，然后输入
your groovy script which is hella greedy
你的时髦脚本，这是你好贪婪
in our case let's start the application
在我们的例子中，让我们启动应用程序
sir it'll start the server and tell you
先生，它将启动服务器并告诉您
that it's in development mode and it's
它处于开发模式，并且
ready to start accepting requests so
准备开始接受请求，因此
we're going to request against local
我们将要求针对本地
hosts 50/50 if you read the log here
如果您在此处阅读日志，则主机为50/50
which is the default port for rat-pack
这是rat-pack的默认端口
you should see
你应该看到
hello groovy it's a show additional
大家好，这是一个额外的节目
verbosity here same deal you know
这里的冗长你知道
plaintext care set in utf-8 now what I
utf-8中设置的明文护理现在我
want to show you in some is a bit of
想要告诉你一些
that prototyping and and
原型和
user-friendliness developer friendliness
用户友好开发人员友好
here so we can actually start modifying
在这里，所以我们实际上可以开始修改
this application while it's running and
该应用程序正在运行时
we'll see the results immediately so if
我们将立即看到结果，因此如果
we were to change this from hello
我们要改成你好
everybody - hello rat-pack save this
大家-您好，老鼠包保存此
file you know we're not touching the
您知道我们没有碰到的文件
groovy stuff and we just issue a request
时髦的东西，我们只是发出一个请求
again turn off that flag yellow wrath
再次关闭该标志黄色愤怒
hack this is really conducive to rapidly
hack这确实有利于迅速
prototyping let's say a REST API that
假设是一个REST API，
you know defines a couple of endpoints
你知道定义了两个端点
and you know could return canned
而且你知道可以返回罐头
responses that you eventually replace
您最终替换的回复
with real services and things like that
真正的服务之类的东西
down the road so um the same kind of
沿着这条路走下去
mechanism is available in Java land
机制在Java领域可用
through griddle you just fact like if
通过扒炉你只是事实就像
you were to run you know Gradle run with
你要跑步，你知道Gradle与
- tea this would enable continuous mode
-茶将启用连续模式
tea - tea is the short name for it
茶-茶是它的简称
continuous is a long name for the flag
连续是该标志的长名称
but basically as long as used as long as
但基本上只要
you're telling Gradle where your main
你告诉Gradle你的主要
application could be running or what the
应用程序可能正在运行或
name of the main classes Gradle will
主要类别的名称Gradle将
take care of compiling everything
照顾一切
starting the application and as long as
启动应用程序，直到
you're passing this continuous flag as
您正在传递此连续标志为
you make modifications to your source
您对源进行修改
code it will reflect those changes
代码，它将反映这些更改
immediately the one caveat here is that
立即一个警告是
any modifications to build scripts or
对构建脚本的任何修改或
settings or anything like that
设置或类似的东西
any kind of Gradle based files like
任何基于Gradle的文件，例如
adding dependencies or removing
添加依赖项或删除
dependencies it
依赖它
take effect until you stop this command
生效，直到您停止此命令
and run it again so that's the one
并再次运行它，那是一个
caveat that you should be aware of let's
请注意，我们应该注意
tell the world in groovy let's take a
用groovy告诉世界，让我们来
look at what a comparable example looks
看一个类似的例子
like Java so coming back to our coming
像Java，所以回到我们的未来
back to our project setup here this is
回到我们的项目设置，这里是
kind of like the minimal minimal Grayle
有点像最小的最小格雷
configuration that you would need to get
您需要获取的配置
a Rat Pack application up and running
Rat Pack应用程序启动并运行
you don't actually really need any of
您实际上并不需要任何
these dependencies here I'm declaring
我在这里声明这些依赖
the plugins through griddles
通过扒手的插件
experimental plugins closure it allows
实验性的插件关闭功能
you to bring in the Rat Pack Java
您带上Rat Pack Java
plug-in which will apply things and make
插件将应用事物并制作
your daily development workflow nice
您的日常开发工作流程不错
again you know we're referencing version
再次，您知道我们正在引用版本
1 - oh and another plug-in that we're
1-哦，还有我们要使用的另一个插件
bringing in is a plugin that's published
带来的是一个已发布的插件
by John Engelmann called a shadow plugin
John Engelmann撰写的一个影子插件
and if you're familiar with maven the
如果您熟悉Maven，
shade plugin it accomplishes the same
它实现相同的阴影插件
thing it produces a single artifact that
它产生一个单一的人工产物
has all of your transitive dependencies
具有所有传递依赖项
and packaged into a single artifact so
并打包成一个工件
that you can have a single artifact to
您可以拥有一个工件
ship around to really convenient I
运送到我真的很方便
highly recommend that you use it if
强烈建议您在以下情况下使用它
you're using any kind of a executable
您正在使用任何类型的可执行文件
jar based application so let's take a
基于jar的应用程序，所以让我们
look at what that same hello world would
看看那个世界你好
look like and in rat-pack
看起来像老鼠装
this is basically it if we compare the
如果我们比较一下，基本上就是这样
groovy version to this one you'll see
groovy版本，您将看到
that what we have in common is this
我们的共同点是
handlers method and this get method and
处理程序方法以及此get方法和
we're making liberal use here of lambdas
我们在这里自由使用lambdas
a number of rat pack API that's exposed
许多公开的Rat Pack API
to the user often taken actions or
给用户经常采取的行动或
blocks of code just something that is
代码块就是
maybe given something it's maybe not
也许给了一些东西，也许不是
given something and something happens
给某事和某事发生
within that so you notice here like get
在那里面，所以你在这里注意到像得到
X handler and handlers takes an action
X处理程序和处理程序执行一个操作
which is given a chain
这给了一个链
even the rat-pack start server which
甚至Rat-pack启动服务器
builds a Rat Pack server finds it to
构建一个Rat Pack服务器找到它
some local socket and just starts
一些本地套接字并开始
accepting traffic this takes a servers
接受需要服务器的流量
Rat Pack service specification which
Rat Pack服务规格
tells you how to build up a Rat Pack
告诉你如何建立一个鼠包
server so in this case we're telling it
服务器，所以在这种情况下，我们要告诉它
hey like for all incoming get requests
嘿，喜欢所有传入的获取请求
against the root path we want to just
相对于我们想要的根路径
render out hello world to it and to show
向它呈现问候世界并展示
that that this does indeed do this do
确实做到了这一点
the same thing as a groovy application
与常规应用程序相同
we'll just load you can see the startup
我们将加载您可以看到启动
rather quickly we are listening on port
我们很快就在港口上听
fifty fifty and just show that but on
五十五十，只是表明，但
that yep we got hello world so again you
是的，我们有了世界你好
know since I'm focused IntelliJ through
知道，因为我专注于IntelliJ
you know right click run on this main
你知道右键点击这个主
method we're not going to get the reload
方法我们不会获得重载
functionality here you need to invoke
这里需要调用功能
griddle run continuous in order to get
扒炉连续运行以获得
that but um the reason I'm doing at this
但是，嗯，我这样做的原因
place because I have a number of classes
的地方，因为我有很多课程
with static main methods that I want to
与我想要的静态主要方法
run side by side so that's basically
并排运行，基本上
hello world rat-pack in a nutshell for
简而言之，您好世界老鼠包
Java and groovy what I want to do at
Java和groovy我想做什么
this point is start introducing the
这是开始介绍
various components that you as a Rat
作为老鼠的各种组件
Pack user would come in contact with
包用户将与
every day and we kind of went over some
每天，我们有点过了
of the names and concepts very quickly
名称和概念很快
but I'm just going to share my notes
但我只想分享我的笔记
here so in the resources that are
在这里，在资源
available to you in the on 24 UI you'll
您可以在24个用户界面中使用
have a link to my presentation notes so
有我的演讲笔记的链接，所以
this will be here this is just hosted on
这将在这里，这只是托管
my github repository under the spring
我在 Spring 下的github仓库
Rat Pack 2016 repository and we're
Rat Pack 2016存储库，我们
specifically at the meet the API section
特别是在“见API”部分
so here I've outlined some of the major
所以在这里我概述了一些主要的
components that you would come into
您会遇到的组件
contact with in your tenure as a Rat
在您的任职期间与大鼠联系
Pack application developer and you know
打包应用程序开发人员，您知道
I've got links to Java Docs and
我有指向Java文档的链接，
everything so should um let's
一切都应该让我们
if we start at the top we've got
如果我们从顶部开始，
something called a handler the handler
称为处理程序的东西
is just simply this interface it's a
只是这个界面而已
void get the handle and praten works and
无效获得手柄和Praten的作品和
it's given some kind of context whatever
给出了某种上下文
the context is it's a Sam type meaning
上下文是Sam类型的含义
it's a single abstract method type which
这是一个单一的抽象方法类型
means you can use lambdas in its place
表示您可以在其位置使用lambda
so you'll see that the rat-pack API has
所以您会看到rat-pack API具有
a lot of these Sam types which make it
这些山姆类型很多
really conducive to writing really
真的有利于写作
concise applications that you can tell
您可以告诉的简明应用程序
what it's doing at a glance the handler
处理程序一目了然
is also the primary means of request
也是请求的主要方式
processing so the handler is the actual
处理，因此处理程序是实际的
bit of code that you can you know read
您知道的一点代码阅读
things from the request write things to
从请求中写东西到
a response like set a cookie or whatever
诸如设置cookie或其他任何响应
and and either return a sponsor or
并返回赞助商或
return a response at that point or
在那时返回响应或
delegate to the next handler down down
委托给下一个处理程序
the chain so in this rat pack hello
链子，所以在这个老鼠包中你好
world example the handler is this bit
世界示例处理程序是这个位
right here this is some this lambda
在这里，这是一些lambda
expression so you know we're given a
表达，所以你知道我们得到了一个
context and context has this render
上下文和上下文具有此渲染
method whatever that is and you just
方法是什么，你就是
give it an object and it will render
给它一个对象，它将呈现
that back to the user in this case so
在这种情况下返回给用户
rat pack has something called a liqueur
老鼠包里有一种叫做利口酒的东西
rendering and parsing framework as long
渲染和解析框架
as you provide support for an object you
当您为对象提供支持时
can just simply call render and it'll
只需简单地调用render就可以了
render it according to how you tell it
根据您说的方式渲染它
to render it we have basic support for
渲染它，我们对
care sequences or obviously because
护理顺序或显然是因为
we're patching a string in here so let's
我们在这里打一个字符串，所以让我们
talk about the context in this lambda we
在我们讨论这个lambda的上下文
have an object that we a alias as DTX
有一个我们作为DTX别名的对象
which is really the context object the
这实际上是上下文对象
context object is the primary means of
上下文对象是
reading request and response objects the
读取请求和响应对象
context is how you get to the actual
上下文是您如何到达实际
HTTP request and response objects and to
HTTP请求和响应对象以及
just clarify here these are not the
只是在这里澄清这些不是
request and response objects from the
来自的请求和响应对象
servlet api these are our own HTTP
servlet API是我们自己的HTTP
request and response objects we still
请求和响应对象，我们仍然
have provide everything that you would
提供了您想要的一切
need headers cookies session information
需要标题cookie会话信息
the context is also the primary means of
上下文也是
inter handler communication and what
处理程序之间的通信以及什么
that means is because handlers can
这是因为处理程序可以
delegate to handlers that are farther
委托给更远的处理程序
down the chain where chain in the
下链的地方
collection are really a linked list or
集合实际上是一个链表或
maybe a graph of handlers it's a way to
也许是处理程序图，这是一种方法
populate that it's a way to like take
填充这是一种喜欢服用的方式
information and add it to the context so
信息并将其添加到上下文中
that the handler down the chain can act
连锁经营者可以采取行动
on that information the context
根据该信息上下文
complaint contains a registry of
投诉中包含一个注册表
application and requests level objects
应用程序和请求级对象
so these are all objects that are
所以这些都是
pertinent to the execution of this
与执行此操作有关
request and then also provides easy
请求，然后还提供了简单
access to really great features of rat
获得老鼠的真正伟大功能
pack which again are parsing rendering
打包再次解析渲染
getting to HTTP concerns and information
了解HTTP问题和信息
about the execution
关于执行
that you're currently in so I mentioned
你目前在，所以我提到
that the contact is a registry well it
该联系人是一个注册表很好
turns out the registry is actually also
原来注册表实际上也是
a thing and rat-pack applications and
东西和老鼠包应用程序以及
registry is something like this so in a
注册表是这样的，所以在
rat pack application we've expanded this
大鼠包应用程序我们已经扩展了它
a bit the new bits are this so from the
有点新的东西是这样的
servlet spec we have a registry method
servlet规范，我们有一个注册表方法
that when you pass it a registry will
当您通过它时，注册表将
start every context execution with this
从这个开始每个上下文执行
registry as its base so for every
注册表作为基础，因此每一个
request that comes in you're going to
您要进入的请求
have a message service which we defined
有一个我们定义的消息服务
down here as a single single method
在这里作为一个单一的方法
interface that just has a string and we
仅有一个字符串的接口，我们
you know we just have our instantiation
你知道我们只有我们的实例化
here which just returns my message
在这里只返回我的信息
service so this is this is an example of
服务，所以这是一个例子
a registry the example of a enterprise
注册表企业的例子
enter handler communication is
输入处理程序通信是
demonstrated here so this chain I've
在这里演示，所以我已经
added a an all-call here so this handler
在这里添加了一个全呼，所以这个处理程序
will be executed for every request that
将针对每个请求执行
comes down the pipeline this means that
下降的管道，这意味着
no matter what kind of request it is no
不管是什么样的要求
matter what path it is no matter
不管走哪条路
you know like what HTTP methods that
你知道像什么HTTP方法
you're giving me I want to apply this
你给我我想申请
logic so you can kind of think of it as
逻辑，因此您可以将其视为
analogous to a servlet filter one I've
类似于我已经完成的servlet过滤器
heard it described before as handlers
听说它以前被称为处理程序
are kind of like servlet filters and and
有点像servlet过滤器，并且
servlets combined but as you can see
servlet组合在一起，但是如您所见
here what we're doing is we're
在这里，我们正在做的是
delegating to the next context down the
委托给下一个上下文
pipeline which is done through this next
通过下一个步骤完成的管道
and with this next we're just adding a
接下来，我们只添加一个
registry with an instant object so
注册表与一个即时对象，所以
finally when we get to our request
最后，当我们达到要求时
processing we can retrieve these items
处理我们可以检索这些项目
that we've registered out of the context
我们已经从上下文中注册了
registry and make additional
注册表并添加其他内容
computations that we need to from here
我们需要从这里开始的计算
so as an example you know like context
例如，您知道上下文
get we call by type and we essentially
得到我们按类型调用，我们本质上
get our type back that we've added to
找回我们添加到的类型
the registry beforehand and this message
事先注册表和此消息
service which we registered at the
我们在
beginning of the rat-pack server
rat-pack服务器的开始
instantiation is also registered in the
实例化也被注册在
context and comes up and we can just
上下文并出现，我们可以
send you know our message as well as the
向您发送我们的信息以及
request at this point and to just
在这一点上要求
demonstrate what this looks like and to
演示这是什么样子并
end we have our application server up
结束我们的应用服务器
and running now and if we again go
现在运行，如果我们再次去
against 5050 we do indeed see that you
针对5050，我们确实确实看到您
know we have our instance as registered
知道我们的实例已注册
by by the by the all handler and then we
通过所有处理程序，然后我们
have our message service message that's
有我们的消息服务消息是
coming from this handler that we defined
来自我们定义的此处理程序
rat-pack server instantiation so that's
rat-pack服务器实例化是
just an information around handlers and
只是有关处理程序的信息，
registries and contexts and all that
注册表和上下文以及所有这些
good stuff so let's talk about
好东西，让我们谈谈
integrating like at this point you have
像现在这样整合
enough information to do some damage and
足够的信息来造成一些损害，以及
rat-pack so to speak and what we'll talk
可以这么说，我们将谈论什么
about at this point is integrating
关于这一点正在整合
existing well integrating spring boot
现有的很好整合 spring boot
that is with rat pack there's kind of
那是与老鼠包一起的
two approaches to this one
这一种的两种方法
is a Rat Pack eccentric approach in
是Rat Pack的偏心方法
which you know use you keep evolving
您知道使用它会不断发展
your application in this manner and what
您的应用程序以这种方式以及什么
you can do is you can take your beam
你能做的就是你可以束腰
definitions and bring them into the fold
定义并将其带入折叠
so and by bringing them into the fold I
所以，把它们折叠起来
specifically mean adding them to this
特别是将它们添加到此
registry here so that they're made
在这里注册，以便他们
available let's shut down our server if
如果可以的话，让我们关闭服务器
we go back to our rat pack configuration
我们回到老鼠包配置
or Gradle configuration you will see
或Gradle配置，您将看到
that we have a rat pack dependency like
我们有一个拉包依赖
compile rat pack dependencies spring
编译Rat Pack依赖项Spring
boot like well what the heck is that the
像靴子一样好启动
Gradle plugin for rat pack that is made
用于制鼠包的Gradle插件
available through this line here exposes
通过此行可用，这里暴露了
this rat pack object that it has this
这个老鼠包对象
dependency method which when you invoke
调用时的依赖方法
it with a string will actually produce
它与字符串实际上会产生
the equivalent of this so so much
相当于这么多
like how we keep our dependencies in
就像我们如何保持依赖关系
lockstep with a Gradle plugin for spring
带有Gradle插件的Spring锁步
boot the same mechanism is also
启动同样的机制也
available in Rat Pack and just like in
可在Rat Pack中使用，就像在
spring food Rat Pack has a number of
春季食品鼠包有一些
modules that you bring into the class
您带入课堂的模块
path to get additional functionality and
获得其他功能的路径，以及
so if you guys start up end up with you
所以如果你们刚开始就和你在一起
know importing a whole bunch of modules
知道导入一大堆模块
in this kind of manner this just becomes
以这种方式，这变成了
like noise and it becomes hard difficult
像噪音一样，变得很难
to read however if you just isolate the
阅读，如果你只是孤立
part that changes and do it like this is
更改并执行此操作的部分是
nice so if you're going to upgrade a
很好，所以如果您要升级
version of rap pack or downgrade it or
说唱包的版本或降级或
do whatever you're never going to miss
做任何你不会错过的事情
out and having compatible binaries so
并具有兼容的二进制文件，所以
this is the mechanism nuts it's a really
这是机制的坚果，这真的是
nice way of keeping the verbosity out
避免冗长的好方法
and making sure that all the binaries
并确保所有二进制文件
are compatible with each other so if we
彼此兼容，所以如果我们
take a look at what a rat pack centric
看一下以老鼠包为中心的东西
application looks like it'll look
应用看起来像
something like this
像这样的东西
so if we go back to our Acme
所以如果我们回到Acme
configuration class just as a refresher
配置类，作为复习
we declared three beans here one the
我们在这里声明了三种 bean
string and then we have two services
字符串，然后我们有两个服务
that are important to our business so I
对我们的业务很重要，所以我
just want to point that out this at this
只是想指出这一点
time that this spring integration into
这个 Spring 融入的时间
rat pack and vice versa is made possible
大鼠包，反之亦然
through mostly through efforts from
通过主要通过
David sire who's a part of the Spring
大卫父亲是 Spring 的一部分
Framework team and it's because of his
框架团队，这是因为他
enthusiasm for rat pack and seeing the
对老鼠包的热情和看到
potentials there that we can thank him
我们可以感谢他的潜力
for having this kind of integration that
有这种整合
allows me to talk to you today about
今天允许我与您谈谈
talking about integrating spring and and
谈论整合 Spring 和
rat pack together so if you are building
老鼠打包在一起，所以如果你正在建造
a rat pack centric application that is
以鼠王背包为中心的应用程序
you are building or server yourself and
您自己构建或服务器，
you are you know defining your chain and
你知道你定义你的链条和
you're building your own registry we do
您正在建立自己的注册表
have available in that rat pack spring
在那个老鼠包 Spring 有货
booth library this spring class and on
春季课及以后的展位库
it is a static method spring which when
它是一个静态方法Spring ，当
you give it a configuration class
你给它一个配置类
we'll take care of building up your
我们会照顾您的
spring application context and adding
Spring应用程序上下文并添加
all those beans into your registry and
将所有这些bean放入注册表
the way we can prove this is by running
我们可以通过运行来证明这一点
this example you can see this message
这个例子你可以看到这个消息
service we don't have a message service
服务，我们没有消息服务
like defined anywhere right where this
就像定义在任何地方
message service is coming in is through
消息服务即将通过
this project level dependency on that
这个项目级别的依赖
artifact on that project that we're
我们在那个项目上的工件
creating so you can see here that we
创建，以便您可以在此处看到我们
have our message service and that we're
有我们的消息服务，我们
expecting it to return an important
期望它返回一个重要的
message but when we move this
信息，但是当我们移动此
application and we run it we'll see that
应用程序，然后运行它，我们将看到
spring boot gets is detected the server
spring boot 获取检测到服务器
starts up very quickly it creates your
快速启动，它会创建您的
beings gets them in the registry and if
生物将它们保存在注册表中，如果
we make a cliff we make a request
我们做出一个悬崖我们提出一个要求
against 50/50 there you go we get our
面对50/50，你走了，我们得到了
important message so this is pretty huge
重要信息，所以这是非常巨大的
you can see that you know if you if you
你会看到你知道你是否
invested you know your tech mind share
投资你就知道你的技术思维份额
and stuff like that into spring and you
和类似的东西到 Spring ，你
have somewhat of a modular separation of
有一些模块化的分离
concerns like layered architecture kind
像分层架构这样的问题
of design and you want to leverage all
设计，您想利用所有
those beings that you have in your in
你内在的那些生物
your company you can bring them in in
您的公司，您可以将它们引入
this matter now if you are using an
如果您使用的是
xml-based configuration there is a way
基于xml的配置有一种方法
to bring that in as well I encourage you
把它也带进去我鼓励你
to go look at spring documentation
去看一下 Spring 的文档
around integrating XML and the Java
集成XML和Java
based configuration for spring but it
基于Spring 的配置，但它
can be done I'm doing it in production
可以完成，我正在生产中
today that is combining Java
今天结合了Java
configuration with them you know spring
与他们的配置，你知道 Spring
application context XML files so it is
应用程序上下文XML文件
possible and it is done so this is what
可能，并且这样做，所以这就是
it looks like to come from a back
它看起来像是从后面来的
perspective if we take a look at what it
角度，如果我们看看它是什么
looks like to come from a spring boot
看起来像是来自 spring boot
perspective is let's just refresh what
视角是让我们刷新一下
what it looks like from the Gradle
摇篮的样子
respect Gradle configuration so you can
尊重Gradle配置，这样您就可以
see the same you know dependency on that
看到一样，你知道依赖
configuration
组态
artifact and here like I mentioned
文物，就像我提到的
earlier because we're not actually
早些时候，因为我们实际上不是
applying the rat-pack plug into this
将鼠尾包插头插入此
application we just bring this in by
应用程序，我们只是将其引入
hand which is no problem and we're still
手没问题，我们仍然
using the spring booth starter for the
使用Spring 展台启动器
web now what this means is that we're
网络现在这意味着我们
actually going to be booting up Tomcat
实际上将要启动Tomcat
and Rat Pack side-by-side so we'll have
和Rat Pack并排放置，这样我们就可以
Tomcat the embedded Tomcat binding to
Tomcat将嵌入式Tomcat绑定到
port 8080 while rat-pack by support
端口8080，同时通过支持进行大鼠打包
50/50 and that looks just something like
50/50，看起来就像
this so if you recall going back to our
因此，如果您还记得回到我们的
Rat Pack HelloWorld application what we
Rat Pack HelloWorld应用程序我们做什么
do is we provide the handlers with our
我们要做的是向处理人员提供
action of chain which is precisely what
连锁的作用到底是什么
this lambda is right here so we're
这个lambda就在这里，所以我们
saying we get a chain we describe how we
说我们有一条链，我们描述了我们如何
want to respond to HTTP requests in
想要回应HTTP要求
spring boot as is the in the fashion and
spring boot 和时尚
style of spring boot all you need to do
spring boot 的风格，您需要做的所有事情
is you know apply your annotation here
你知道在这里应用注释吗
apply your rat pack enable rat pack
应用您的老鼠包启用老鼠包
annotation and just define a component
注释并仅定义一个组件
here which in this case is the action of
在这种情况下，这是
the chain and this chain is just the
链，这个链只是
logic that you care about writing right
您关心正确书写的逻辑
so this is a this is it if we run this
所以这就是如果我们运行这个
code sample here we'll see that it does
代码示例在这里，我们将看到它确实
indeed boot up you should note that
确实启动，您应该注意
because of this annotation spring and
由于这个注释Spring 和
rat pack cooperate to build the rat pack
鼠包合作打造鼠包
server with sensible defaults and it'll
具有合理默认值的服务器，它将
be injected that server will be injected
被注入服务器将被注入
with this action chain and it will be
这个行动链，它将是
able to serve this request on port 5050
能够在端口5050上满足此请求
so we got this message hello from spring
所以我们从 Spring 就收到了这个消息
boot so let's take a look at that's what
开机，让我们来看看那是什么
we expect and indeed it is and we do get
我们期望，的确如此，我们确实得到了
back hello from spring boot just to show
从 spring boot 向你打招呼只是为了展示
that Tomcat is also running we can issue
Tomcat也正在运行，我们可以发出
a request against port 8080 and this is
针对端口8080的请求，这是
exactly what we expected we didn't
正是我们所期望的
define any kind of controller that's
定义任何类型的控制器
binding to the route path here so 404 is
绑定到此处的路由路径，所以404是
exactly what we expect and this is kind
正是我们所期望的，这是善良的
of a the spring boot centric approach so
以 spring boot 为中心的方法
instead of you know writing and defining
而不是你知道写和定义
your
你的
server and taking control of that what
服务器并控制什么
you say is you know I like you know how
你说你知道我喜欢你知道如何
to spring such everything up for me I
给我这样的 Spring
just want to write the component that I
只想写我的组件
care about which is the piece that
关心哪一块是
handles the traffic and that's all I
处理交通，这就是我的全部
want to provide and spring food and Rat
想要提供和春季食物和老鼠
Pack will collaborate to give you this
Pack将合作为您提供
ability now someone you may meet may be
现在您可能遇到的某人的能力可能是
asking like why would you be using
问像你为什么要使用
spring booth and like top of the
春季展位，像
embedded tomcat and Rat Pack
嵌入式tomcat和Rat Pack
side-by-side well I mean there's there
肩并肩好，我的意思是那里
are a lot of reasons I'm one could be
我可能是很多原因的
like differences in the in volume right
就像音量上的差异一样
like if if you have you know if you need
就像如果有，就知道是否需要
to be able to handle a lot of requests
能够处理很多请求
for one specific component of your
对于您的一个特定组成部分
application and perhaps your other side
应用程序，也许你的另一面
the application is doing something like
该应用程序正在做类似的事情
them as like a crud admin or something
他们就像一个粗鲁的管理员之类的
like that that's certainly a use case
这样肯定是一个用例
where you would want to use you know Rat
您想在哪里使用，您知道Rat
Pack and Tomcat side-by-side but here's
Pack和Tomcat并排放置，但这是
an example how are how are you talking
一个例子，你怎么样
and Tomcat running side by side so let's
和Tomcat并排运行，让我们
start with the spring food components
从春季食物成分开始
really a you know through through the
你真的通过
use of the controller or stereotyped
使用控制器或定型
annotation we're binding two paths one
注释，我们将两条路径绑定在一起
is to the route one is to rad pack the
是到路线一是拉德打包
route just returns with the spring group
路线随Spring 组返回
and rat pack creates a rest template and
老鼠包会创建一个休息模板，
issues a request against the rat pack
向老鼠包发出请求
running server and returns out of the
正在运行的服务器并返回
map which should be rendered as JSON and
映射为JSON和
the rat pack chain that we've defined
我们定义的老鼠背包链
we've added two new handlers one is for
我们添加了两个新的处理程序，其中一个用于
the endpoint get JSON and the other one
端点获取JSON，另一个获取
is forget boot and so the JSON simply
忘记了启动，所以JSON只是
creates a map that has a key of date and
创建一个具有日期键的地图，然后
the value of now which is just an
现在的价值只是
instant represented as a string and
立即表示为字符串，并且
again we're using we're making use of
再次，我们正在使用，我们正在利用
the rendering framework in in rat pack
Rat Pack中的渲染框架
and we have first-class support for JSON
而且我们对JSON具有一流的支持
of course which means that we can take
当然，这意味着我们可以
this map and serialize it as JSON
此地图并将其序列化为JSON
setting the appropriate headers and and
设置适当的标题和
you know things like content type and
您知道诸如内容类型和
things
东西
and send that back to the user the end
并将其发送回用户端
point on here called boot will grab an
在这里称为启动将抓住
HTTP client out of the context registry
HTTP客户端脱离上下文注册表
that's provided from rap back server
从说唱后备服务器提供
this is a non-blocking asynchronous
这是一个非阻塞异步
client so when you issue a request
客户，所以当您发出请求时
against when you issuer crossed against
当您的发行人反对时
us spring boots embedded tomcat
美国 spring boot 嵌入式tomcat
container will actually have to like
容器实际上必须喜欢
transform these asynchronous the results
转换这些异步结果
of these asynchronous some types as they
这些异步的一些类型，因为它们
come back and so we're going to get the
回来，所以我们要去
body and once we get the body we extract
身体，一旦我们得到身体，我们提取
the text and say that we receive this
文字说我们收到了这个
from spring booth and then render this
从春季展位，然后呈现此
string back out to the client so just to
串回给客户，所以只是
quickly demonstrate these requests in
快速展示这些请求
flight we'll start up the server and
飞行，我们将启动服务器，
we'll just go through and make our
我们将经历，使我们
request now so first let's take a look
现在请求，让我们先来看一下
at spring booth Oklahoma State 80 this
在俄克拉荷马州80号春季展台上
is spring boot right this is the
是 spring boot 吗，这是
application here let's take a look at
这里的应用程序让我们看一下
the roof request for rat pack now so
屋顶对老鼠包的要求现在如此
that's what we expected this is rat
这就是我们所期望的
packing spring boot we're now going to
包装 spring boot ，我们现在要
take a look at the end point that rat
看看那只老鼠的终点
pack exposes for the rest template
包暴露其余模板
consumption which is just JSON here so
消费这里只是JSON所以
this returns JSON as expected and to
这将按预期返回JSON并返回
demonstrate that we are setting all the
证明我们正在设置所有
headers correctly you can see that on
标头正确，您可以看到
content type is application JSON and it
内容类型是应用程序JSON，它是
is what you're expecting so now if we
是您的期望，所以现在如果我们
make a request against the spring food
对春季食品提出要求
that issues the rest template call to
发出其余模板调用
rat pack we'll see that we get that JSON
rat pack，我们将看到我们得到了JSON
object back which is great and vice
反对，这是伟大的，反之
versa we can also make use of the rat
反之，我们也可以利用老鼠
pack endpoint that proxies a call to the
打包呼叫的端点
embedded servlet container that's
嵌入式servlet容器
listening to port 8080 flat route and
监听8080端口的扁平路由，
this is what we get
这就是我们得到的
and that's what we expect so this is
这就是我们所期望的，所以这是
pretty much just the beginning of how
几乎只是如何开始的
you can integrate these two obviously
你可以很明显地整合这两个
because you have all of Spring Framework
因为您拥有所有Spring Framework
so you go system available to you it is
所以您可以使用系统了
quite easy to figure out like what kind
很容易弄清楚是什么样的
of components can work for your
的组件可以为您工作
particular use case at this point I do
在这一点上，我会使用特定的用例
want to share my list of resources that
想分享我的资源清单
I recommend that you go follow up if
我建议您继续跟进
you're interested in this kind of stuff
你对这种东西感兴趣
obviously the spring initializer is a
显然，Spring 初始值设定项是
definitely go to I have links to you
绝对要去，我有你的链接
know rap back home page are you know
知道说唱回首页吗
github repository for the organization
该组织的github存储库
where we have you know code samples from
我们从哪里知道代码示例
conferences we've spoken at from labs
我们在实验室发言的会议
that we've given hand done workshops
我们已经做了手工讲习班
things like that well we don't have
这样的事情，我们没有
currently or any kind of maven examples
当前或任何种类的Maven示例
building with maven audits should be
与Maven审核建立
trivial to do just no one has done it so
琐碎的事，只是没有人这样做
if anyone would like to issue a pull
如果有人想发出拉
request of building rapid Nathan we'd
建造快速内森的要求
certainly take that for sure we have a
当然可以肯定，我们有一个
user guide I do want to point out our
用户指南我想指出我们的
slack channel as well so our community
频道也很闲，所以我们的社区
is small but it is growing and it is
虽然很小，但正在成长，
quite active so if you just navigate
非常活跃，所以如果您只是导航
over here you can can register and start
在这里，您可以注册并开始
asking questions we have a really good
问问题，我们有一个非常好的
response time around this as well we
响应时间也与此有关
also do have a dedicated forum for rat
也有专门的老鼠论坛
pack users they'll come and ask
打包用户，他们会来问
questions here as well but I do
问题也在这里，但我确实
recommend going to the Select channel
建议转到选择频道
over posting the forum since um you'll
自从您发布论坛以来，您将
also benefit from other people who are
也从其他人那里受益
who may have encountered what you're
谁可能遇到了你
trying to accomplish or have answers to
试图完成或有答案
questions that you may have and last but
您可能遇到的问题，最后但
not least a colleague of mine Dan woods
至少是我的丹·伍德的同事
who is also a core member of the rat
也是老鼠的核心成员
pack team is has finished writing
打包团队已完成写作
learning rat packs so that is done ready
学习老鼠包，以便做好准备
to go and it's off to production
去生产了
it is slated to be out in May so I
它定于五月上市，所以我
highly recommend that you know if you're
强烈建议您知道自己是否
interested in Rat Pack and kind of
对Rat Pack和种类感兴趣
interested in seeing you know what are
有兴趣看到你知道是什么
best practices what are some use cases
最佳实践有哪些用例
I'm Dan Woods has really nice examples
我是Dan Woods，有很多很好的例子
in here and and a very logical and clear
在这里，非常合乎逻辑和清晰
progression of how to use Rat Pack and
如何使用Rat Pack和
all of rat packs features I highly
我所有的老鼠包都具有很高的功能
recommend it if you want to if you're
如果您愿意的话，推荐它
interested in this kind of stuff I've
对我喜欢的这类东西感兴趣
read the whole book and its really great
读了整本书，真的很棒
so and last but not least I know I said
所以最后但并非最不重要的一点是，我知道我说过
that before but for real now I do have
以前，但实际上，我确实有
all of my presentation notes available
我所有的演示文稿都可用
in my github repository under spring rat
在我的github仓库中，在spring rat下
pack 2016 again and all the code samples
再次打包2016和所有代码示例
that that you saw today are also
你今天看到的也是
available and a my and my notes here
可用，这里有我和我的笔记
also go through everything that I've
也要经历我所经历的一切
discussed with you today thank you for
今天和你讨论过，谢谢
your time well I'll take questions now
好的，我现在就去提问
excellent thanks Danny all right so
非常感谢丹尼，好吧
first one is from Daniel and I'm not
第一个是丹尼尔的，我不是
going to try to pronounce this last name
将尝试发音这个姓
so Daniel asks you know so Tomcat is
所以Daniel问你知道，所以Tomcat是
your default run right let's say JBoss
您的默认运行权限，例如JBoss
but you know how about even with the
但是你知道即使
need to reconfigure I had already
需要重新配置我已经
answered that then yeah sure you can run
回答，那么是的，您可以运行
on undertow um but regarding the need to
在欠费，但考虑到需要
reconfigure wouldn't that sort of depend
重新配置不会那种依赖
on whether they're doing like a embedded
他们是否做得像嵌入式
jar file or a war file a kind of
jar文件或war文件
deployment or it or is it just you have
部署，或者只是您拥有
to recompile you know when you know
当你知道的时候重新编译你知道的
that's right like if you're yeah I mean
是的，就像你是的，我的意思是
if you're using an embedded servlet
如果您使用的是嵌入式Servlet
container I'd say that you're pretty
我会说你很漂亮
insulated from swapping out the the
避免换出
actual server container that you're
您所使用的实际服务器容器
using whether that's Tomcat or JBoss or
使用是Tomcat还是JBoss还是
jetty or or um you know undertow but if
跳船或你知道吗，但是如果
you are producing a war file for an
您正在为
external standalone server container
外部独立服务器容器
which we actually do at our company then
然后我们实际上在公司做
you you actually need the classes that
你实际上需要的课程
inform spring Bhutan how to interact and
通知春季不丹如何互动和
configure how Tomcat should be running
配置Tomcat应该如何运行
so those are specific to the servlet
所以这些是特定于servlet的
container of your choice so you probably
您选择的容器，因此您可能
would have to recompile and change the
将不得不重新编译并更改
classes that you use there yes cool all
在那里使用的课程是很酷的
right Daniel hopefully that addresses
对丹尼尔希望那地址
your question um there's only one other
你的问题嗯，只有一个
question this time actually um so folks
这次实际上是问问题，所以乡亲们
if you have others this is the moment
如果你还有其他人，那是片刻
Ryan
瑞安
Vaughn from IO high-tech America asks
IO高科技美国公司的沃恩问
can you define multiple at B action King
您可以在B动作王中定义多个
wait a minute oh I'm sorry that
等一下哦，对不起
characters got all funky in there we go
角色都变得很时髦
okay I didn't expand it's right let me
好吧，我没有扩展，对吧，让我
repeat that I apologize so Ryan is just
重复我的道歉，所以瑞安只是
asking you to find multiple being action
要求你找到多个存在的行动
chains like a NAT being annotation and
像NAT这样的链被注解
then action chain hey Ryan that's
然后是动作链，嘿，瑞安
actually a really good question
其实是一个很好的问题
I hadn't I don't know why I haven't
我没有我不知道为什么我没有
thought of that off the top my head you
想到那顶我的头你
can certainly define multiple beams in
当然可以定义多个光束
terms of how the actual spring
实际 Spring 的条件
integration with Rat Pack is going to
与Rat Pack集成将
pull that in I'm not sure how that will
把它拉进去我不确定如何
play out but um as far as just being
发挥出来，但就目前而言
able to define them of course you can in
当然可以定义它们
terms of how that impacts like what
诸如此类的影响如何
actions actually get sound that all I'm
行动实际上得到了我的声音
afraid I'll have to actually look into
怕我必须去研究一下
that got it Uncle John maybe that's
得到了约翰叔叔，也许那是
something maybe that yeah cool maybe
是的，也许很酷
that's something you can also pick up on
您也可以选择
on Twitter I believe you had your your
在Twitter上，我相信您拥有了自己的
Twitter handle that's beginning of your
Twitter处理就是您的开始
presentation so that's uh that's
演示文稿，所以，那是
something maybe you can pick up Ryan
也许你可以拿起瑞安
with with him on on the Twitter's Daniel
和他一起在Twitter的Daniel上
Nathanson from after rack asks you know
机架后的纳森森问你知道
he's considering using rack rat pack
他正在考虑使用机架式鼠尾包
with spring cloud and it's wondering how
与 Spring 的云，它想知道如何
support for things like service
支持诸如服务之类的东西
registrations in Eureka type stuff would
在尤里卡类型的东西中注册
work um spring cloud would register with
Spring Cloud 将向工作UM注册
the port of the Tomcats
Tomcat的端口
but clients using that service would
但是使用该服务的客户会
want would still want to sort of use the
想要仍然想要使用
neti port right so how would that work
neti端口正确，那将如何工作
sure I have to have to admit like my
确定我必须像我一样承认
interaction with spring cloud is very
与 Spring Cloud 互动非常
limited so in terms of that I don't have
有限，所以我没有
a definite answer
一个明确的答案
working with what I've just demonstrated
使用我刚刚展示的内容
you can certainly have spring boot or
你当然可以有 spring boot 或
the embedded tomcat server if you're
嵌入式Tomcat服务器（如果您是
using it forward all requests to the
使用它将所有请求转发给
underlying Rat Pack server which I mean
基本的Rat Pack服务器，我的意思是
you may not want to do that but it'll
您可能不想这样做，但是它将
work
工作
for the use case right the other thing
对于用例，另一件事
is that I would I would probably think
是我可能会想
that you could configure that port
您可以配置该端口
actually through either a property file
实际上通过一个属性文件
or through some kind of um kind of value
或通过某种形式的价值
that you pass the annotation but I
您通过注释，但我
thought I would just I would just go to
以为我会去
stack overflow let's have one for Google
堆栈溢出，让我们为Google准备一个
yeah yeah I know I wish I had some more
是的，我知道我希望我有更多
insight there to I'm trying to remember
我想记住的洞察力
what I've seen in the Eureka console and
我在Eureka控制台中看到的内容以及
whether or not they they pass through
他们是否通过
port numbers those services in ug
端口号ug中的那些服务
Service registration um hmm oh that's a
服务注册，嗯，哦，那是一个
good one uh sorry about that Daniel
很好，对不起，丹尼尔
maybe we can yeah maybe Stack Overflow
也许我们可以，也许堆栈溢出
is a good place or if you want to
是个好地方，或者如果您想
address that to the at spring cloud open
解决在 Spring Cloud 开放时
source handle it Springs out of source
源句柄从源头弹出
handle Witter I'll just hold on let me
我会坚持下去让我继续
just pop it into the console here so
只需将其弹出到控制台中即可
that you can not have to remember write
你不必记住写
down the handle okay all right so yeah
放下手柄好吧，好吧
let's punt on that one and I need me try
让我们在那上面踢一下，我需要我尝试
tweeting it and I'll see if the other uh
发推文，我看看其他人
spring cloud engineers can perhaps come
Spring 的云工程师也许可以来
in from there um shalash keaney asks uh
从那里开始shalash keaney问呃
sir Danny what do you recommend
丹尼爵士，您有什么建议
spring boot centric or Rat Pack centric
以 spring boot 为中心或以Rat Pack为中心
there's a loaded question but no hey
有一个问题很多，但是不，嘿
yeah that's uh that's quite a heavy
是的，那是很重的
question there
在那里提问
I would actually you know it really
我其实你真的知道
depends on like where you're coming from
取决于你来自哪里
right so it I would say this comes down
对，所以我会说这下降了
to your use case so if you are a spring
到您的用例，所以如果您是 Spring
oriented JBM shop which I would say
我会说面向JBM的商店
accounts for most of the most of the
占大多数
Java based shops out there most likely
基于Java的商店最有可能
you have most likely you already have
您很可能已经拥有
your spring beans configured and
您的Spring bean 配置和
packaging some kind of nice jar right so
包装一些不错的罐子吧
if that's the case and your team is open
如果是这样，并且您的团队很开放
to experimenting and playing around with
尝试和玩耍
you know building the actual Rat Pack
你知道建立实际的老鼠包
server yourself I would recommend going
服务器自己，我建议去
down Rat Pack and pulling in spring if
向下拉鼠群，并在春季拉动
you are a spring boot for a shop and you
你是一家商店的 spring boot ，你
want to perhaps maybe play around for a
也许想玩一个
packer not so committed to it yet but
Packer尚未对此作出承诺，但
you want to see if if you like the look
你想看看是否喜欢它的外观
and feel of it I definitely recommend
和感觉，我绝对推荐
doing the spring boot centric approach
做以 spring boot 为中心的方法
you know this is also like in scenarios
你知道这也像场景
where you already have a spring good
你已经有一个 Spring 的好地方
application but you find a use case for
应用程序，但您找到了一个用例
handling you know large amounts of in
处理你知道的大量
inbound volumes that maybe for some
入站卷可能对于某些
reason you don't want to switch to
您不想切换到的原因
undertow or or put like nginx or
像nginx或
something like that in front of it that
在它前面的东西
could kind of handle that for you
可以为您处理
yeah so it depends it depends on your
是的，这取决于您的
preference how how adventurous you're
偏好您的冒险程度
feeling and and what your company's like
感觉以及您公司的状况
in terms of like what the like what are
就喜欢什么而言
your artifacts look like that you're
你的文物看起来像你
producing and are you spring food
生产，你是春季食品
already yeah I think that's a pretty
是的，我认为那是一个漂亮的
balanced response I mean because that's
平衡的反应，我的意思是因为那是
it's a very open-ended question and you
这是一个非常开放的问题，你
know yeah you tend to get answers like
知道是的，你倾向于得到像
it depends when you when you ask for
这取决于您何时要求
blanching stations uh so um again Daniel
烫烫站，呃，再来，但以理
Nathanson who had the question on on
纳森森（Nathanson）提出了问题
spring cloud a second ago is following
一秒钟前的 Spring Cloud 正在跟随
up and saying hey is is Rat Pack
并说嘿是Rat Pack
considering adding support for
考虑增加对
distributed tracing you know stuff like
分布式跟踪您知道诸如
a stray sword after pickin um you know
捡起之后的流浪剑
spring cloud sleuth uh provide this but
Spring 的云侦探呃提供这个，但
it doesn't you know we we don't support
你不知道我们不支持
Rat Pack sort of ingress and egress
Rat Pack进出的种类
points yeah that's actually a really
是的，实际上
good question we do have an open ticket
好问题，我们确实有一张公开票
on integrating distributed tracing I
集成分布式跟踪I
think for us we have an issue open with
想想我们有一个问题
perhaps looking at Zipkin and pulling
也许看着Zipkin并拉
that in and getting that working but um
进入并获得工作，但嗯
I mean if you are up to implementing
我的意思是如果您愿意实施
that and and adding that functionality
并添加该功能
to Rat Pack like we'd be more than happy
对Rat Pack就像我们会很高兴
to have that I think that's something
有我认为那是某事
that we would need I think there are
我们需要我认为
some discussions on our github issue
关于我们的github问题的一些讨论
tracker right now yeah we we do cool we
追踪器，现在是的，我们很酷
do want it that's for sure in another
确实希望在另一个
comment by the way on the spring cloud
顺便评论一下Spring Cloud
thing from Daniels spring cloud question
Daniels Spring Cloud问题中的内容
he was just commenting yes you can you
他只是在评论是的，你可以吗
know there is configuration to change
知道有需要更改的配置
the port but then the health check and
港口，然后进行健康检查，
point provided by actuator wouldn't you
执行器提供的点不是吗
found all right yeah of course stuff
找到了所有的东西当然
yeah because that's all going to get
是的，因为这一切都会得到
better right because that's pretty
更好，因为那很漂亮
important right right right yeah that's
重要对对对对
not nervous it's getting registered in
不紧张，它正在注册
Eureka right it's like the thing you're
尤里卡，对，就像你
you're you're writing a getting
你在写一个越来越
registered within the system you know
在您知道的系统中注册
actuator bolts ports you know now maybe
您现在知道的执行器螺栓端口
you could somehow register those and
你可以以某种方式注册那些
services to that could be weird but um
对此的服务可能很奇怪，但嗯
yeah maybe Daniel maybe try hitting up
是的，也许丹尼尔也许会尝试
the at spring cloud open source a handle
Spring Cloud开源的一个句柄
for that one and hopefully um you know
对于那个，希望你知道
maybe we can even can help you figure
也许我们甚至可以帮助您确定
that out but or Josh long Starbucks man
那还是乔希·长星巴克的男人
no he's got some experience back to I
不，他对我有一些经验
know five seconds I don't know so I do
知道五秒钟我不知道，所以我知道
want to point out that Rat Pack does a
要指出，Rat Pack可以
metrics module in particular we
指标模块，特别是我们
integrate with drop wizard metrics so
与拖放向导指标集成，因此
however you reporting that you can
但是您报告您可以
configure an endpoint for your metrics
为指标配置端点
and perhaps you can point it to use that
也许您可以指出使用它
end point instead of actuator and you
终点而不是执行器，您
could also um you could also forward
还可以，你也可以转发
requests from from wrap back to this
从包装返回到此的请求
form good actuator endpoint although I
虽然我形成了良好的执行器端点
don't know how useful that would be
不知道那有什么用
since actuators looking also at servlet
因为执行器也在看servlet
statistics right
统计权
but for other things like any any kind
但对于其他任何事物
of custom metrics that you have that are
您拥有的自定义指标
not you know trim the container specific
你不知道修剪容器吗
would certainly benefit from you know
肯定会从你知道中受益
having that request come in through Rat
通过Rat收到该请求
Pack yep
打包是
oh cool um one of the one of these a
哦，酷，嗯，这些之一
mark puckett I guess is uh actually just
马克·帕克特，我想是
published a little piece of code there
在那里发布了一些代码
like an actual rapper um that looks like
像是一个说唱歌手
yeah it looks like it just so that's
是的，看起来就像这样
cool Wow
酷哇
dynamic oh yeah coming in over a webinar
动态哦，是一次网络研讨会
that awesome okay that is actually like
真的很棒，就像
that total make sense in ten years
十年之内，这个总数才有意义
that's awesome this guy you just won the
太棒了，你刚刚赢得了
webinar award buddy
网络研讨会奖状
way to go mark hahaha that's that's
标记马克哈哈哈的方法就是这样
really cool yeah that totally makes
真的很酷，完全可以
sense so what Mark is showing here is
感觉，所以马克在这里显示的是
that um you have access to the actual
那个你可以访问实际的
actuator endpoint and and all the data
执行器端点和所有数据
associated with it so from rat-pack land
与它相关联
you should just be able to iterate
你应该只能够迭代
through that and it looks like you're
通过那看起来你
using groovy here but uh but yeah the
在这里使用groovy，但是嗯，是的
principle stands that you can go through
原则上讲，你可以通过
the actuator endpoints and find what you
执行器端点并找到您
need which is yeah awesome okay yeah I
需要，是的，太棒了，是的，我
mean and you really yeah you can code
是的，你真的是的，你可以编码
food apps with groovy as well but yeah
groovy的食物应用程序也不错
totally
完全
so um cool well that's a super awesome
非常好，这真是太棒了
thank you Mark that's wonderful awesome
谢谢你，马克，太棒了
to see that okay well I think that seems
看到好吧，我认为这似乎
to have exhausted the question queue I'm
用尽了我的问题队列
going to start doing is just a little
要开始做的只是一点点
bit of housekeeping work and then you
一点家政工作，然后你
know a question wall if you look at it
看看问题墙
on so we are recording the the this
因此，我们正在记录这个
events it will be posted to spring dot
事件将被发布到spring dot
IO /a video and also spring that IO
IO /一个视频，也可以播放该IO
/blog usually within about two weeks at
/ blog通常在大约两周内
the outset hopefully I can like tie but
一开始我希望我能喜欢领带
that's that's sort of what we that's our
那就是我们的那种
service level agreement at the outset um
一开始的服务水平协议
and the the replay and
和重播和
normally it would be sliced but boss
通常会切成薄片，但老板
Danny here did all demo and slide so um
丹尼在这里做了所有演示和幻灯片
we'll we'll have that post for you to
我们将为您提供该职位
share with your your colleagues and you
与您的同事和您分享
know go over if there's something that's
知道去看看是否有什么事
that you missed that you want to check
你错过了要检查的地方
out on if you travel a lot a YouTube
如果您经常旅行YouTube
downloader can be a great way to take
下载器可能是一种不错的选择
these webinars with you on the rows and
这些在线研讨会与您一起
watch them from your tablet or what's
从平板电脑上观看它们或什么
that what have you while you're on the
那你在的时候有什么
point um so with that I think if you're
要点，我想如果你是
looking for bits and software you know
寻找您知道的位和软件
just realize that we you know we used to
只是意识到我们您知道我们曾经
have HTTP downloads enabled on the
在上启用了HTTP下载
spring website we cut that off a few
春季网站，我们减少了一些
years back and really try to encourage
几年前，并尝试鼓励
you to download it by maven or Gradle if
您可以通过maven或Gradle下载它，如果
you you are on a military network or a
你在军事网络或
closed network or left behind 200
网络封闭或落后200
letters of proxy servers and you
代理服务器和您的来信
desperately need HTTP downloads for some
迫切需要一些HTTP下载
reason you can get them you can get
你可以得到他们的原因你可以得到
ahold of spring booth from repo dot
回购点的春季展位
spring dial and repo or EPO
Spring 拨回购或EPO
repo dot spring that IO and that is our
IO的回购点Spring ，这就是我们的
artifactory serve both our nightly build
人工制品服务于我们的每晚构建
and it is a way that you can get HTTP
这是获取HTTP的一种方式
downloads not easily mind you but you
下载不容易引起您的注意，但是您
can get them um so uh yeah um and then
可以让他们嗯，所以嗯嗯，然后
Danny what's this way to get hold of
丹尼（Danny）以什么方式掌握
zone Rat Pack a bit I'm it I saw your
区域Rat Pack有点我看到了你的
Gradle example before um that Gradle is
um之前的Gradle示例是
best way for you to absolutely yeah all
绝对是的最佳方式
of our stuff is an artifact tree and and
我们的东西是神器树，并且
Nexus I'm sorry in maven central so if
Nexus对不起，在Maven Central中，如果
you do if you do need to grab the
如果您确实需要抓住
artifacts I'm not sure if we host the
我不确定我们是否托管
the artifacts to github I should check
我应该检查的github工件
that but that that may be a dead end
那但那可能是死胡同
actually oh yeah through artifactory and
哦，是的，通过人工制品
at the J Center and and maven central
在J中心和Maven Central
actually um well excuse me I think
嗯，好吧，我想
that's it um just quick comment or
就是这样，只是快速评论或
actually smart it is a bit a little bit
其实很聪明，这有点
more of a question from Josh Kinney
Josh Kinney提出的更多问题
he-hey we gonna have another webinar for
嘿，我们将再举办一次网络研讨会
more advanced topics like Rx is history
像Rx这样更高级的话题是历史
etc is this in relation to
这是关于
rat-pack or just in general uh we we
老鼠装还是一般来说，我们
assume rat-pack considering the title of
假设考虑到
the webinar but I'm sure leche if you
网络研讨会，但是我敢肯定，如果您
want to clarify that on the chat that
想要在聊天中澄清一下
would yeah it would be great if there's
是的，如果有
interest me from we certainly had lots
我当然很感兴趣
of webinars on spring clouds um and yeah
春季和春季的网络研讨会的数量
okay he did say rad pack yeah that's my
好吧，他确实说过rad pack是的，这是我的
thought right it's just checking so yeah
认为正确，只是检查所以
Danny what do you think as long as
丹尼只要你有什么想法
there's enough interest for it I'd be
我有足够的兴趣
happy to talk about rat pack and all the
很高兴谈论老鼠包和所有
various modules that we have there is a
我们拥有的各种模块
lot of material and framework
很多材料和框架
integration from our site as well so
也可以从我们的网站进行整合
there's a lot to go over I mean yeah I'd
有很多事情要做，是的，我会
be happy to do it for sure well squeaky
很高兴做到这一点
wheels get the grease thanks for thanks
车轮得到润滑脂，谢谢
for asking Charlotte maybe with them
问夏洛特也许和他们在一起
Danny why don't want you and like to
丹尼（Danny）为什么不想要你，喜欢
talk about that and and maybe we can get
谈论这个，也许我们可以得到
something on the books on you know I
你书上的东西知道我
think you did a great job today and I
认为你今天做得很好，我
I'd be happy to have you back and um
我很高兴你回来
yeah so let's let's talk about doing
是的，让我们来谈谈
exactly that I think that'd be cool all
完全是我认为这很酷
right great
太好了
thanks for the thanks for the interest
感谢您的关注
to us yeah and then alright so I think
对我们来说，然后好吧，我想
that's about it folks
就是这样
um let's wrap it we're a little bit
嗯，把它包起来，我们有点
after the hour sorry for that but we
一小时后抱歉，但是我们
really do try to make extra time and
确实确实尝试腾出更多时间，
thank you for doing that Danny but we
感谢您所做的丹尼，但我们
really do always try to make extra time
确实总是尝试争取额外的时间
for your questions unless it gets
您的问题，除非它得到
ridiculous you know like a half an hour
半个小时你就知道了
after the webinar then usually we start
网络研讨会之后，通常我们开始
to cut it off but um yeah so Danny
切断它，但是嗯，所以丹尼
anything you want to say before we call
您打电话之前要说的话
it I think um this has been great
我觉得这个很棒
no I hope I had at least succeeded in
不，我希望我至少成功
taking your interest in checking out
带您去结帐
wrap hack and seeing how spring food and
打包一下，看看春季食物和
Rat Pack are not mutually exclusive
Rat Pack不互相排斥
you can definitely use them together in
你绝对可以一起使用它们
any kind of capacity awesome
各种能力都很棒
I totally agree thank you so much and
我完全同意，非常感谢
yeah wonderful mom let's let's talk
是的，很棒的妈妈，让我们谈谈
about maybe doing another topic I think
关于我想做的另一个话题
that could be cool thanks everyone
可能很酷，谢谢大家
appreciate your time and attention and
感谢您的时间和关注，
your questions have a wonderful day
您的问题有美好的一天
and catch you on the next webinar
并在下一次网络研讨会上与您见面